Guide to the Mixed Company of Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Mixed Company of Yale records
1986-2008
RU 1077
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(3 boxes)
The records consist of sheet music, advertisements, clippings, photographs, scrapbooks, and other memorabilia of Mixed Company at Yale.
Mixed Company (Musical group: Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations..
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from Mixed Company of Yale, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Separated Materials
Commercial audiorecordings were transferred to the Historical Sound Recordings Collection, Yale Music Library.
Biographical / Historical
Mixed Company of Yale was founded in the fall of 1981.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of sheet music, advertisements, clippings, photographs, scrapbooks, and other memorabilia of Mixed Company at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material.
Students' songs; Vocal groups; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Mixed Company (Musical group: Yale University); Yale University -- Songs and music; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Mixed Company of Yale records, 1986-2008; Accession 2008-A-156
  - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Concert programs, 1987-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flyers and posters (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1986-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Photographs
    - Snow job, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Snow job, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbooks
    - The Many Faces of Mixed Company, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Rush Album, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Mixed Company...A Year in Review, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Mixed Company...A Year in Review, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Mixed Company - The Gump, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Mixed Company - Our 25th Year, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sheet Music (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
  - Tours, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Unplugged, production master, 1993 July 2; 1 (Box 2)
  - Unplugged, duplication master, 1993 July 2; 1 (Box 3)